def question_bank():
    json = {"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What are the chest muscles called",
                                             "correct_answer": "Pectorals",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Abdominals", "Biceps", "Deltoids"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which of the following is an exercise for the pectoral muscles?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Bench Press", "incorrect_answers": ["bicep curl", "leg press", "running"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which of these training schedules is the bro split?",
                                             "correct_answer": "one muscle group a day",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Push, pull legs", "cardio", "fullbody"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which of these exercises targets the back more than others?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Pull up",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Push ups", "Overhead press", "Sit ups"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which of these exercises targets the legs more than others?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Lunges", "incorrect_answers": ["Bent over rows", "Crunches", "Side lateral raises"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Where is the tricep located??",
                                             "correct_answer": "Upper Arm",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Chest", "Back", "Upper leg"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Where is the trapezius located?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Upper back",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Shoulder", "Lower leg", "Upper leg"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "How many reps should one shoot for in order to build muscle?",
                                             "correct_answer": "8-10",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["2-3", "12-15",
                                                                   "20"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "How many reps should one shoot for if they're trying to lose weight?",
                                             "correct_answer": "12-15",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["2-3", "8-10", "20"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "How many calories does the average adult need to eat per day to maintain their weight?",
                                             "correct_answer": "2000 - 2500", "incorrect_answers": ["1000-1500", "2500 - 3000", "3000 - 3500"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Pick the healthiest breakfast meal?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Eggs and oatmeal with fruit",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Egg, bacon, sausage, toast and beans", "Bagel with low fat cream cheese", "Pop Tarts & black coffee"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What are isolation exercises?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Exercises that only target one muscle group", "incorrect_answers": ["when someone works out at home", "working out at the gym", "Cardio"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which of these exercises would require a spotter more than the others",
                                             "correct_answer": "Bench Press",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Bicep Curls", "Sprint intervals", "Body Squats"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Where are the quadriceps located?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Upper leg",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Upper back", "Upper arms",
                                                                   "Lower leg"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which of these should be done before every workout?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Warm up/stretch", "incorrect_answers": ["Shower", "Take pre-workout", "eat"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which one of these exercises targets more major muscle groups?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Deadlift",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Bench press", "Shoulder press",
                                                                   "Calf raises"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which exercise boosts metabolism the most out of the following?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Strength training",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Pilates", "Yoga", "Kickboxing"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What does HIIT stand for?",
                                             "correct_answer": "High-Intensity interval training",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Heat", "High-Interval intensity therapy", "High-Interval Intensity training"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "Which of these is the biggest muscle in the upper arm?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Tricep",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Bicep", "Deltoid", "Quadriceps"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "How often should you train to maximise muscle gain?",
                                             "correct_answer": "4-6 days a week",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["3 days a week", "Once a month", "Once a year"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What is a calorie surplus?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Eating more than you burn",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Eating less than you burn", "Healthy calories",
                                                                   "vitamins"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "How important is nutrition when training to loose weight?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Very important",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["not important", "somewhat important", "what is a diet?"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What type of exercises build the most strength?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Compound exercises",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Isolation exercises", "cardio",
                                                                   "yoga"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What is the name of the diamond shaped muscle in the back that is worked when performing rows?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Trapezius", "incorrect_answers": ["Abdominals", "Hamstrings", "Biceps"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What type of exercises uses body weight for resistance in a rythmic manner?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Calisthenics",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Yoga", "Pilates", "Weight lifting"]},
                                            {"category": "Sports", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy",
                                             "question": "What is hypertrophy?",
                                             "correct_answer": "Increasing muscle Fiber",
                                             "incorrect_answers": ["Increasing your workout", "Increasing fat",
                                                                   "Increasing Calorie Intake"]}]}
    return json
